and then my dad tested a couple years
later and I got to beat him up uh but of
the 10 people in my family eight
siblings and two parents um one two five
of us are black belts
wow that's
insane so uh so yeah you could you you
you all can whoop a few people's asses
so I I I'm sure you have a lot of
confidence now yeah and and that's the
key
a quick mic check for me y mic check one
two check
check M check one two perfect thank you
testing testing testing one two three
um in the place to be it's Ryan Perez La
La
La testing one two3 Perfect all right
okay we're going
live what if there was a docu series for
entrepreneurs that never ended a living
documentary that will continue to
clarify illustrate and unfold
information about the culture that
surrounds
entrepreneurship what if this docu
series was filmed in front of a live
audience all over the world where
censorship and editing were no longer
applicable when information that is
given to you isn't packaged but
delivered to you raw and fresh honest
and truthful what if you could ask
questions live or help fact check while
someone is speaking well we have already
created this platform and we call it
hustle Zone TV
[Music]
[Applause]
hey what's going on folks this is the
hustle Zone and I am your host Ryan
Perez owner and founder of bowy
creative.com uh we are company that does
more meaning we don't build websites we
build online businesses so you know make
sure you guys check out my website ww.
creative.com uh you know to see what
we're all about and what our premises
about building online businesses because
our our our websites are pretty much all
inclusive you know you get everything
you get a
CRM uh you get email marketing you don't
have to pay for um additional services
so uh you definitely want to check it
out and then we also do free
consultations um if you have any
questions even about your website so
definitely check that out and um this is
brought to you by branding jim.com and
branding Jim is a a company that we are
launching pretty soon giving people
unlimited graphic designs so
um uh you'll definitely want to check
that out as well so if you head over to
that website sign up to the subscriber
um or to sign up to our news newsletter
uh will'll let you know when we launch
and of course this is hustlez own.tv and
um or hustle Zone TV but you guys can
check out this interview and many other
interviews on ww. hustlez own.tv um but
yeah we're and I and and I'm I'm going
to say we're the first living
documentary you know we're documenting
the lives of entrepreneurs we're
revealing more than that's why you see
the plus sign a lot of people are like
is that hustle zon you know they're
trying to pronounce it it's hustle Zone
the plus means we don't want any zeros
we want the variable because we there's
just so much um to hustle Zone but you
know the most important thing to hustle
Zone and the why uh that we do this is
that we want to document
stories of entrepreneurs we want to
provide free education to um uh to you
to you all that want to learn more about
becoming entrepreneurs you know this is
not a business platform this is an
entrepreneur platform so this is the
more of the creative side of building
businesses just giving you the
motivation but also giving you the nuts
and bolts behind a lot of people's
stories so that you can apply to your
life you know the third point is that we
develop we want to develop future
entrepreneurs because I was telling my
guest um you know in the in uh in The
Green Room that you know I want my son
to be able to look at his interview one
of these days and say wow you know you
mean I can do that so that that is the
most important um part of of this this
platform and then number four honest
content you know we are attempting to do
factchecking live so having the ability
to put up facts as people are speaking
um you know that is a goal of ours that
we want to do but when and we're still
working on the technology to be able to
do that but in the
interum you guys if you you you if you
if you find that um that I'm saying
something that's not factual put it up
on the screen and we'll correct it you
know that's the whole point and and we
we do put your comments on the screen
just be respectful and uh don't put
people's personal information um you
know because well and and and and mind
you I probably wouldn't put it up
anyways but you know we definitely want
to provide that honest content and we
want you to feel a part of the show um
as much as possible so how's everybody
doing uh I'm going to check to see who's
in the room right now holy cow six
people already good Lord we got um hold
on a second here I can't even scroll up
we got Robert we got Brent we have
xanadoo in the house we got sha Dell in
the house we got Jason Barts we got
Jesus Monica Shondell Shandell thank you
for the shout outs today I really
appreciate that um hold on one second
why why is my name not showing um and
then we have Alex Flores uh we have um
Phil and and and Julian so how are you
folks doing uh I'm going to see if we
can get your comments on the screen here
so I'm just going to test sometimes this
works sometimes it doesn't and then we
got Sean shanell says I I believe you're
from Brooklyn is that what you're saying
there let's
see Facebook comments please come up on
the screen there we go yes you're from
Brooklyn and
um she says love it you're awesome well
you're awesome and Let Me Tell You Folks
my guest is awesome you know um it the
way that like you guys remember that
amazing interview uh by uh Andy AET he
came on and he gave us a fantastic
interview he's such a standup guy that
he went out of his way to to um uh to
find this guest to to introduce him and
I together so that he can be on this
show and this guy is like a celebrit to
me I mean like anytime I see people that
um are in kind of the same business that
I'm that I'm doing but they are doing um
exceptionally well you know I definitely
want to interview them because you know
you never like these guys are really
busy these guys have a lot of things on
their plate and for for and I feel so
honored that my guest um would even
think to come on to the hustle zone so
you know you guys are definitely in a
treat tonight I read on his website that
you know he's like I and and this is his
Market this is his I think is his
personal website and he was like you
know
I started off
broke but then he became a motivational
speaker he became an entrepreneur he's a
social media and brand strategist okay
so you know the reason why we do the
hustle zone is because it's not about
where you start it's about where you
finish it's about execution you know I'm
and I'll say this I'm an entrepreneur
for life you know and I may quit on
ideas but I don't ever quit on being an
entrepreneur because sometimes ideas
don't work and you have to be able to
know um that it's that you're just
pouring in um your resources into
something that's not working and it's
okay to quit those ideas because you're
just going to lose money but the the
essence and the spirit of being an
entrepreneur I'll be an entrepreneur
until the day I die so I'm going to
continuously build businesses and build
um opportunities and and and and hire
people so that we can build better
communities so he is a definition of
someone that is helping a lot of people
I mean you know just doing my research
today and looking at all of the people
that um that he's helping out and you
know looking at some of his speaking
videos he is so engaging so I definitely
want you guys to give a round of
applause
four Mr AJ Adams how's it going my
brother hey Ryan how's it going I
appreciate the uh the generous
introduction I love your energy oh thank
you well you you deserve it you deserve
it and and uh tell us a little bit about
D6 media yeah absolutely so D6 media uh
is interesting how it came about I think
I honestly believe like the best
businesses come out of either necessity
or just the discovery of something
amazing so D6 media came out of both of
those things when I started as a
motivational speaker and I don't I don't
use that title anymore I actually don't
like that title because I don't care
about getting you motivated I want to
get you to take action and that's how
I've always approached speaking and I
think action motivates people but D6
media came from when I started as a
speaker had no idea what I was doing
didn't know how to Brand myself didn't
know how to Market myself I that social
media was the the next platform that
that I need to be on but I didn't know
how to use it properly I wasn't active
so I had to learn it myself I didn't
couldn't afford to pay someone to do it
so I learned social media had to create
content had to build a website how to
Market myself I obsessively studied
about branding and marketing and uh the
this consumer psychology and ended up
getting pretty decent at it to get
myself booked on stages connect with
people in network and then maybe two
years into that business my wife was in
my ear saying you know you really need
to speak on branding that's what you're
good at because I was getting the itch I
never felt like motivational speaking
was the fit for me I felt like something
was missing and so she you know being a
Lov and supportive wife she saw that and
was always thinking okay what what do he
really do well so she was in my ear
branding social media I said no I
haven't proved myself I don't have a
large of following blah blah blah and
then I started to get other speakers
other entrepreneurs asking me questions
about my social media my online presence
in fact I had one entrepreneur reach out
to me who was even more successful than
me and asked hey can you recommend a
social media manager because I see your
social media and I need someone who's
who's doing yours and I messaged them
back and said I do it myself so not not
long after um maybe a couple years later
we launched D6 media which was this past
May so we're we're in startup mode uh
but using the strategies that we teach
our clients we took a small budget of
$26 just doing some testing on Instagram
and Facebook and some other uh strategic
processes and we turned that into uh a
little over $20,000 in client contracts
in the first about 45 days of the
business and since then we've gotten the
attention of some much bigger players in
The Branding space and we're actually
negotiating now a major partnership deal
that's going to open up a whole another
level uh for us to work with high level
celebrity clients so 28 is going to be a
big year for us woo that's that's that's
that's crazy well um and I I wish you
luck with all of that because I mean
it's a tough business and it's there's a
lot of people in this business you know
especially the younger guys that are
like yeah you know I'm going to make
$5,000 a month and you know um and they
go off on that path and they they take
all the webinar courses and then all of
a sudden they're a brand strategist but
you know it it I think people know like
really quickly you know if you are who
you say you are and if by your results
and if you can't if you can't if you
can't help them with their bottom line
then you you pretty much lose out in
this business it's not an easy business
to maintain especially I don't know are
you a kind of guy that works uh you know
day and night or like how's your how's
your schedule look like
normally uh so I do attempt to take a
day off on Sundays uh my wife gets upet
with me because sometimes I I I'll be
doing things on social media uh but
generally you know I I stop usually in
the evening around dinner time but it
really it's it's we're in startup mode
so um you know entrepreneurship has no
set hours it's more about aligning
what's important so there are times that
I work later times I work all night um
there are days that I I won't work in
the morning and I'll work later in
afternoon just depends on what's going
on with family um what I do focus on
what I learned a long time ago is to
focus not on the to-do t ask or how much
time you're spending but on getting the
results so that's where that's how I
gauge things now that's like the primary
kpi that we use awesome so uh we have a
tradition here on the hustle Zone and
and a lot of the people the fans um they
would be U mad at me if I did not
mention this
um what is your story I mean it's a very
generic question but we want to know
from when you were young as far as you
can remember and bring us up to from
where you started to who you are
today yeah absolutely so um you know and
I've gotten pretty good at telling my
story because the story is what matters
especially when you have a personal
brand you know we both understand this
with branding we talked a little before
the show in the uh the virtual green
room but the story matters so much and
so many people Overlook it it's kind of
like going to the gym you know I started
back at the gym last night so I I'm in
pain now people I am sore all all over
my everything but I know that in two
weeks doing these same workouts it'll be
nothing and I'll forget how difficult it
was we do the same thing with our story
we've overcome the challenges so we
forget how difficult it was and when
someone asks what's your story We Tell
just the the biggest highlights but we
forget to really share the impact and
the significance and really paint the
picture to bring someone into the story
and that's where Brands you know Miss
opportunity and they don't engage so my
story I'm just a shy kid from a tiny
island in the middle of the Pacific I
grew up I was born in San Diego family
moved to uan when I was a kid and uh I
grew up there we were there about 10
years until I was in my late teens and
we moved back to Southern California but
growing up I was not a confident kid I
got bullied in school and I remember in
second grade there was a kid named
Javier and he was my school bully first
day of school I got a brand new shirt
and my parents have a lot of money so
when I got a brand new shirt it was a
big deal like this it was I felt I was
looking good first day of school he took
a highlighter walked up to me for no
reason and just rode on my shirt wow I
was devastated you know second grade I'm
what what is that seven eight years old
and I remember just trying to hold back
tears because I didn't already didn't
have a lot of confidence and I went to a
really you know ghetto School in Guam
and I'll tell you how ghetto it was that
same kid this is where everything
changed for me in terms of my confidence
I went home that day told my dad this
kid was picking on me and my dad who's a
martial artist he looked at me and said
the next time he puts his hands on you I
want you to kick his and he told me what
to do so I went back to school and I
beat him up now I started as a
motivational speaker speaking on
bullying so that's not a real popular
solution yeah but I'll tell my son the
same thing if he puts his hands on you
and I told my 13-year-old daughter you
lay him out you put him to sleep so and
that's not a popular opinion I don't
care it worked and the I say it's a
ghetto school because the teacher
allowed it she actually encouraged it
because she hated this kid so much
that's how bad the school was so we uh
we ended up fighting and um I won the
fight and from then on I never let
anyone pick on me uh I had one other
fight after that in second grade same
year but as an adult and through my teen
years I never got in a fight uh
excluding the fights that I jump into to
stop the fight and help a stranger which
happened twice interestingly enough um
and never got to thank you but it's
whatever but yeah that was me as a kid
so growing up you know we had typical
things I I was in public school I didn't
get picked on anymore I learned to
develop a sense of humor to you know
talk the bullies down um in the sense
that I would actually confuse them I I
was real sarcastic and I'd have someone
who said I'm G to beat you up I'm going
to do this and I literally laughed at
them and start making jokes to the point
where they couldn't take themselves
seriously anymore and they just walked
away so I've always been good with my
words and persuasion and getting in
someone's head to convince them to do
what I wanted them to do and then uh
yeah in my then my parents took me out
of school I was homeschooled and that's
where things got kind of bad in terms of
Education um I was already not a good
schools my parents weren't Educators and
there were times they couldn't afford to
pay for the curriculum so long story
short I struggled in school I didn't pay
attention and in my third year as a
sophomore you guys can do the math and
my 30d years of sophomore I uh dropped
out of high school and just quit I was
done I didn't see any point and that
continued I dropped out of I eventually
got my GED uh and I'll give you my
definition of a GED now uh but I dropped
out a three colleges because it just I
just didn't see how it worked for me so
I just I I didn't take the quote unquote
right steps to be successful in terms of
formal education and didn't come from
the right kind of family that should
lead to success my ethnicity my
socioeconomic situation my upbringing I
mean everything statistically said that
I should be dead homeless a thug in jail
um you know whatever not happily married
for going on nine years with three kids
and building successful businesses and
the reason why is because I had some
great people in my life I had great
mentors one in particular that g who
gave me a book and uh I have it
somewhere here in my office but he gave
me a book about this young kid that grew
up in an island just like I did and went
on to become this International
evangelist travel speak impact the world
and he gave that to me in May of 2000 so
it's been 17 over 17 years now almost 18
years and in it he wrote me a note but
the one line that stuck out that I
wouldn't really realize the impact of
until 12 years later at like
28 he wrote me a note that said AJ it's
not about the location it's about the
heart and what he was telling me lesson
I learned later was that where you are
doesn't determine who you are where you
are doesn't determine who you are you
can take control of your life and you
can write your success story and I the
moment I learned that and let me let me
know if I'm going too long but the
moment I learned that was when I was
sitting in the parking lot of a Taco
Bell restaurant with my wife and then
two daughters myself wasn't born yet
with my wife and two daughters and I was
literally re-evaluating my
life now people listening probably
thinking okay you you're sitting at a
Taco Bell restaurant reevaluating your
life like what kind of burrito did you
have and I'll tell you why I was
reevaluating my life because I had just
gone the drive-thru and the uh tell the
cashier told me that my car was declined
I checked my bank account there's no
money in fact I was negative about2 200
some dollars and I realized I had just
moved my family to Southern California
to uh start this youth program at a a
French Church they brought us on board
and I have nothing I have less than $6
to my name we found a bag of change in
the car $538 that's everything we had to
our name and I realized then why that
was the hard moment I needed to realize
that the reason for it was that I had
been a passive character my entire life
just reacting and that's what happens to
a lot of us when we grow up broke we
grow up poor we grow up abused we grow
up in circumstances that tell us and a
society that tells us well you don't
have the right family the right
education you're not the right ethnicity
you don't live in the right geographic
area you're not going to be successful
so I just reacted I was in surv mode and
that day I decided you know what it's
enough from now on I'm taking control
this is not the story I want I'm going
to write my success story so from then
on I decided who I wanted to be and it's
evolved from you know just Tak care of
my family to be a millionaire to now my
goal is to be a billionaire in the next
before I'm 60 maybe 50 and um I started
aligning my goals with that uh life went
on from that Taco Bell restaurant I
ended up working two jobs one of which
was working as a janitor scrubbing
toilets for you know barely above
minimum wage hated the job but every day
I sat down and I was writing and I I
actually wrote my first book as a
janitor I wrote a book on success that
is now the book that is the basis of the
talk that I give in my motivational
talks and the reason I wrote a book on
success when I wasn't successful was
because I believe that I would one day
stand on stage and tell the story of how
I wrote that book before I was
successful
of how I decided I would be successful
before I was successful because I knew
that nothing would emphasize the point
nothing would be greater proof of what I
was going to say than to be able to say
that I decided then I would be
successful
now so scrub toilets worked with the
janitor life went on eventually uh we
moved back to Arizona and um I took odd
in jobs I sold cars I worked at a
startup as a salesperson so that company
fell apart um I did other jobs I can't
remember at this point and eventually
you know we my wife and I worked our way
up to from $6 to six figures and then we
I got more speaking engagements uh
triple my speaking fees because I worked
on my branding and then we launched D6
media and now we're here and we're we're
about to do bigger things than we've
ever done things that are are above and
beyond what should really even be
possible at this Point wow so yeah there
you go wow what a story I mean um first
question because you know I kind of grew
up similar to you in the sense that I
was bullied um I was bullied a lot um
when I was younger especially in the
city that I'm in in Canada here by the
way zanadu wanted to know before I uh
ask the next question but she wanted to
know what uh where are you from in the
states or where are you located I'm in
Phoenix
Arizona okay you're in Phoenix okay
hopefully that answered your question go
ahead and I am from the states but
people often ask me and this may be what
she's actually asking people ask me AJ
where are you from like you look so much
like Dwayne The Rock
Johnson and I I'll joke with people and
I tell him you know I'm I'm his younger
sexier brother but uh I'm half Pacific
Islander and I'm half African-American
so my mom is from the islands my dad is
from Texas so I say that I'm half
American awesome African American this
is the first time I heard that um so
okay I was bullied I you know so I know
what that how that feels and you know it
made me very angry um as a kid um how
did you like how did you feel during
those times and because I mean it
sounded like you know there was just a
you know a few events that have happened
in your life and you seem to be
uh a calm Collective you know individual
how did you you know like how did you
deal with a lot of those
emotions so um again having great
mentors uh one One Mentor that I had
early on who I learned from uh as a
speaker uh was Josh ship and one of the
things he says is every kid is just one
caring adult away from being a success
story so I I had those caring adults in
my life uh my dad being one of the
earliest influences uh I had a pastor
who was a mentor um and he was a doctor
naval officer uh and he was an
entrepreneur so I I gleaned a lot from
him um and then later in life you know I
had there were lots of stages to
building my confidence to where it is
now um and I've redefined confidence my
my present day definition of confidence
is knowing that I'll get it done even
when I don't know how I'll get it done
and honestly if you don't have that you
won't be a successful entrepreneur
because you're you're doing you're
building something that doesn't exist
from something that may not exist um so
those influences but also um you know I
said my dad was a martial artist well
eventually he and I both went back to
training I earned my black belt uh and
you know Blood Sweat and Tears I mean
literally I got jumped by about 30 other
black belts to earn mine and then my dad
tested a couple years later and I got to
beat him up uh but of the 10 people in
my family eight siblings and two parents
um one two five of us are black belts
wow that's
insane so uh so yeah you could you you
you all can whoop a few people's asses
so I I I'm sure you have a lot of
confidence now yeah and and that's the
key that's the key when you know what
you're capable of I remember going home
after earning my black belt feeling so
confident and part of me was like I wish
somebody would try something in this
airport right now
let a terrorist try something let me
take him out but at the same time when
you're confident in who you are and what
you can do it gives you humility
especially if you had to fight and and
be humble to earn that so I got the mess
beaten out of me literally I had
internal bruising to earn my black belt
so I have no desire to fight anyone
because I know that one it's not worth
it two I don't have to and if you force
me to it's going to be a very bad
situation for you and prob possibly
other people so now the next question I
have for you is um you know you starting
off um the way that you did I think it's
uh same way I did because I I started
four years ago I started in this
business and um just because my woman
left and I needed to pay the bills and I
just I was working at a marketing you
know company at the time and I saw that
they made a half a million uh in one
year just selling websites and I was
like hm
I'm G to become a web I like that model
I mean I was doing graphic design for 15
years but the uh you know that that
whole stretch of you know um and and I I
I made probably within the first 45 days
around that I made 10 grand but and and
that was a lot because I was working
retail probably majority of my life so I
was like whoa this is crazy um this is a
lot of money
so you know why would you take that
plunge to get to become an entrepreneur
cuz I as and I'm only talking about my
story because you know I thought I was
crazy I thought I was going to be poor I
thought I was going to be homeless and
you
know there what the for me I was I was
uh I I couldn't even gather my thoughts
I was living every day in fear that
something bad would happen how were you
feeling going through this transition in
your life um it's the hardest thing I've
ever done um you know a lot of people
will say when you I remember when I left
my day job um and I left my day job
it'll be two years and may next year so
it's been a little over 16 about 20 it's
about 16 months now 18 months and when I
I was speaking part-time and I realized
I had to leave because I was starting to
get more speaking engagements but I
didn't have any PTO left and I've always
been a top performer any job I've done I
obsessed about it I become the best at
it and I was bringing in you know as a
sales person um I was bringing in
$150,000 a month on average in Revenue
that's what I was bringing in in
contracts that's what I was bringing
into the company but we worked on salary
not commission so I was only making
about 40 45 and I was
outperforming by you know a factor of
two supervisors in the company I I had
my managers asking me how to be a better
leader because of my leadership
experience and the influence they saw I
had with the team and I just got to a
point where I said you know I went to
them and said can I take untime unpaid
time off I've got these speaking
engagements I was very transparent about
it and they said no we can't do that so
I had a choice either cancel my
contracts with my clients for these
speaking engagements or I leave my job
and I take the leap so I left my job and
uh you know some people will say well
when you leave your day job and to
become an entrepreneu entrepreneur you
got to hit the ground running uh no for
those of you who haven't done it you
will not hit the ground running you will
hit the ground rolling you will get Road
hauled through life for as long as it
takes before you achieve any success it
will it will ruin relationships people
will doubt you uh you may your it will
test you I mean I I would have so much
preferred to have taken that leap when I
was single because being married makes
it more 10 times more difficult being
having kids makes it a 100 times more
difficult because now when you're a
single guy I can go live on my go move
back with my parents go live on a
friend's couch for almost no money but
when you have a family you have other
lives that you could ruin so it puts the
pressure on but it you either break or
you step up and you execute so I said i'
give you a different definition of GED
today GED to me means go execute daily
and that's what it's about you just have
to it's going to be hard my I've had to
go to the food bank I've had to borrow
money I've had to take title loans out
my car I had to sell a car to pay rent
um I gotta you I all those things but
you do it in spite
of I I you know because this that's the
other thing you're in a business that is
not there's not a lot of cash flow that
comes through the business you know
you're dealing with contracts on time to
time you may get a 10,000 20,000 or even
a 50,000 but that runs up pretty quick
you know especially when you have to
hire employees and you have to do all
these other things so you know um can
you let how how does one manage you know
you get into this business but now how
do you manage and how do you keep things
afloat so that you know you're not
depending on that contract to end you
know because a lot a lot of people go
after that big number but they don't
understand that you're not going to get
it all upfront that's for sure yeah I
mean so some of it you know we we we're
we've adjusted our business model based
on some of those things we looked at the
industry in The Branding space and not
just the design we we our team does
websites and all of that but um we
looked at the factors of the the
strategy and how to avoid the pitfalls
of contracts and long-term projects that
are lots of time not a lot of money so
now when we do a branding project we
don't spend more than a week on it we'll
get a brand completely built out in
about a week and of course it depends on
the project but if it's A5 $10,000
$20,000 project we get it done quick um
then we have our retainer clients so
again we're in startup mode so we're
we're building all this out and we're
testing um but the way to manage it is
you you've got to get mentors you've got
to get people who are further along than
you who've made more mistakes than you
have and who've built a business that's
twice as large at least than the
business you want to build so if you
want to build a six-figure business get
a mentor that's built a seven figure
business you want a seven figureure get
one that's built an eight figure so I
have mentors who built eight and nine
figure businesses and those are the
people I reach out to when I have
questions um and then when I when I
first left my day job and took the leap
I didn't work as hard as I I worked as
hard as I thought I needed to which was
a mistake I should have worked 10 times
harder than I thought I needed to so I
would actually have more business than I
could handle so when you take that leap
if you think you need to make 10 calls a
day send 10 emails a day do 50 like
overwork yourself so that you're
stacking up because you don't know what
pits are going to come and then you know
your process get the right processes in
place in the right systems um so that
you can avoid a lot of those headaches
payments being held up um and don't be
cheap invest in the right things invest
in the right people invest in the right
coaching um perfect example when I was
speaking I was when I started out I was
speaking for like 500 bucks a talk and
then it got up to you know 1,500 and
then I got a a coach who gave me just
one or two key things that I did and I
more than doubled my speaking fee and
going into 2018 I'll double it again and
by the TW end of uh end of 2018 um the
goal is to be uh at you know a higher
five figure sum for speaking
engagements now I understand what it
takes to do that because of the
processes and systems and things I've
learned through making so many mistakes
and a coach helps you learn those
without making all the mistakes
yeah that's that's that's a great way of
looking at it uh uh zanadu asked uh what
is your um I guess I'll paraphrase it
what is your perspective on
intuition uh intuition so people call it
different things that inner voice that
gut um for me intuition um my wife has
that in fact I I'm GNA I told her and
I'm not joking I'm going to get a tattoo
that's that has an
like a disclaimer and it said it'll say
all my best ideas come from my wife
because really in our business most of
my best ideas have come from her either
by inspiration or the application so uh
but intuition um for me it's been Faith
uh that's a driving force of everything
I do it's a foundation it's a rock that
I stand on and it's why I have the
mission I have and that hasn't changed
since I was 14 years old it's been to
help people what has changed is how I
execute that and what that looks like
and it's gotten bigger and bigger and
bigger um so uh intuition is important
but you've really got to pay attention
to what the intuition is based on
there's a very fine line between faith
and stupidity and 99.99% of the time
they both look the
same now um a deeper question here
relationships dealing with relationships
when you know you want to slay uh slay
the dragon you want to make a million
dollars a billion dollars I've been in
that situation as well and that's why I
went broke because I I came home I'm
like I'm gonna start a business and she
was like you ain't starting nothing with
me so you know she uh you know pretty
much it was uh she felt insecure and and
she she left moved in with her with her
mom and I was stuck here alone with my
dream now um and I heard you some key
wordss there that you brought up about
relationship so you know did you go
through something similar in a sense
where you had to break up a marriage
because of your commitment to your
business or did you have turmoil and how
did you get out of it you know so that
you can find peace um so definitely had
T turmoil in all relationships um but
I'll speak specifically to
marriage pre-marriage in marriage and
and post so um I chose my wife based on
what I who the woman I knew I would need
to who would be crazy enough to go with
me so I had three very specific things
went through a really bad breakup um a
couple a few years before and U didn't
date at all uh I had dated one girl for
I went went on on one date but never
seriously dated anyone after that
breakup and I got really clear a lot of
time in meditation and prayer and uh
counsel of wise people mentors and the I
came up with three criteria and I'll
tell this to everyone out there l don't
worry about what he looks like guys it's
not about that the character is what
matters and I said I want a woman who
has very strong faith loves Jesus want
has a heart to serve people and then
will follow me wherever I go because
there has to be a solid foundation that
we resonate with in terms of the core
beliefs that drive we are and it doesn't
have to be Faith some there are some
people watching this who that's not a
factor for you but the core principles
that you live by have to resonate with
the other person if they don't if you
view the world so differently that it
clashes you don't have to be the same in
everything my wife and I don't agree on
everything but the most important thing
is the non-ego pools we absolutely agree
on then you've got to have someone who
has the same U motivation or Mission as
you uh if they don't want to grow a big
business then it may not work out youve
got to know that going in if you're 22
years old and you want to start a
business and be an entrepreneur I would
suggest don't get in a relationship
don't get married until until you've
established yourself because that
entrepreneurial road is hard you will
crawl through you crawl through crap and
you will walk through fire and that's
just how it is and not every man every
woman it has what it takes to go through
that now on the flip side with my wife
because I picked the right character
traits I didn't even realize I just knew
that's what I needed because I
anticipated doing something big and that
would be crazy so when I jumped she
jumped with me not always uh willingly
sometimes I had to drag her along
because what I was doing was crazy but
she's at the point now where that's my
queen that's my ride or die and
she you know I'm I will never leave her
because no one she is crazy there were
times in our marriage when we were
struggling when I was working as a
janitor that I told her to her face
you're stupid for marrying me you should
divorce me because I'm a
loser and by all standards I was right
but she didn't and so now you know I
teased her said she gets reap the
benefits and I told her I'm going to
make you a millionaire but it's going to
be because she's gone through this with
me so you've got to pick someone who is
strong enough to go through it with you
and if you don't know how to do that
then stay single be married to your
business and your dream establish
yourself and along that road you'll find
someone you'll find someone who has that
drive who's in those circles who gets it
uh if you don't it's just going to be a
nightmare
now a personal question for you and kind
of off topic but when discussing money
and talking about money especially if
money doesn't always come
through what are in your household what
are those conversations
like um so they're very different now um
my wife is my wife is the MBA she used
to handle she used to handle all the
finances until we got you know in
entrepreneurship and the bank account
started looking really shady and uh not
shady in the sense of you know unethical
but in the terms of there's a lot of red
numbers a lot of zeros a lot of negative
numbers uh so I said let me take over
the finances but the the core of it you
know with that question it comes down to
this finan is the number one thing that
drives couples apart that often leads to
infidelity that just ruins
marriages it's trust is key so my wife
trusts me because I've learned I have to
have very transparent communication
what's happening what's going to happen
where we're going and it's it's in
leadership in general the most difficult
place to lead a spouse or a team or your
your uh your employees is not through
adversity not through uh losses it's
through ambiguity when they're looking
for you and saying what are we going to
do to pay the rent what are we going to
do to get more clients and all you can
say is I don't know that's when it comes
to the relationship Equity that you
build that's what we call a de media the
relationship Equity if you haven't built
enough trust and relationship with them
you have nothing to bank on when you
don't have answers so you either have
answers or you have
relationship and you have to have both
because when you don't have the answers
the only reason they'll follow you is
because they trust you that you will
figure it out and that's why in the most
difficult Financial conversations
sometimes I've said look babe I don't
know trust me I'll get it
done wow that's crazy so folks what he's
saying here relationship Equity answers
or relationship you know and it boils
down to um you know it boils down to
outcomes
because desires can't be
measured there desires are just Concepts
but you know answers are deliverables
action is deliverable you can measure
that but you can't measure all the
hypotheticals so um man that that's
that's brilliant now um in terms of do
you like I understand you you know you
have a you know your your work schedule
kind of depends on what's going on and
and whatnot but where do you see
yourself in you know when it comes to
spending time with business and and
whatnot where do you see yourself in
five
years uh wow five years so I'll say
where I see myself but I'll be very
honest and transparent with you and the
audience uh it's going to be way off
base because I'm I guarantee I'm
shooting too low uh a year from now I'll
be looking back on this conversation and
saying I don't know what I was thinking
that's that's way too low uh but in five
years uh we'll have aund million company
D6 media will be a what is that 10
figures 10 figure company uh we'll be
working very high level clients uh you
know celebrities and Fortune 500
companies um uh business will have grown
exponentially uh I plan to have a large
company with a lot and employ a lot of
people very passionate about that of
providing jobs and providing a work
environment that's phenomenal awesome
all the best things that you'll find at
companies like Google and um Facebook
and a lot of these very um upto-date
relationship centered oriented companies
uh that's a passion of mine and my
wife's and honestly we're just not built
for anything smaller I'm just not having
a sixf figure income and a seven bigger
business that's that's that's basic to
me uh I want to go big you know my my
three goals in business are are help
people get rich and give generously in
that order so five years yeah I I want
to put Gary vaynerchuck out of
business well that's a that that's
definitely a good good goal to have uh
so zanadu says how are you incorporating
your children in your entrepreneurship
I tell I tell tell my 13-year-old
daughter all the time I say watch what
we're doing watch what I'm doing pay
attention and we we were very
transparent with them a lot of parents
feel like they have to keep their kids
in the dark with through financial
struggle and all that no we bring our I
mean depending on their age our
13-year-old daughter she's in those
conversations a lot more than her
younger siblings are because she can
comprehend it and she can process it um
so we bring her in and I'll tell her
here's what's happening here's this deal
here's what we did do you see what's
happening um because she she she was
there when there was nothing and she's
been there through the Journey and now
she sees you know for example this big
deal that's happening she knows what's
happening with the deal she knows the
people involved and how significant it
is because I a lot of people they become
successful and their kids end up spoiled
and ungrateful because they never saw
the process so my kids will have the
advantage of not starting from nothing
like I did but I want them to see the
process because they either need to stay
humble and be effective and impacting
the world in a positive way they either
need to have the experience which they
won't have like like I am and my wife
are is or they need to have the the
knowledge of seeing the process so
that's one way the other way is uh we
don't pay our kids for doing chores not
we stopped doing that uh some time ago
what we do is we pay them for reading
books so my daughter's read she right
now she's reading the 10x rule by Grant
Cardone she read a the last book she
read was called badass your brand about
branding she's read she read the
millionaire booklet um you know we have
for reading things like that she'll read
Rich Dad Poor Dad and depending on the
complexity of the content and the size
of the book that determines how much she
gets paid so Rich Dad Poor Dad thick
book pretty complex Financial concepts
for you know a high schooler I'll give
her I'll pay her hundred bucks for that
and then that's how she'll make her
money and now she's already she's
already started her little business
she's got really into to cosmetology and
doing Nails she read a book earned money
she went and bought a whole nail salon
kit she she been practicing how to do
the little jail nails and whatever her
girls do and now she's starting to try
to book her friends for for nail
appointments she did a whole menu of
different services and the prices and
she's starting her little
business wow that's that's amazing so uh
and I I do that with my son because it's
it's kind of you know um I think a lot
of people think that Business and
Entrepreneurship are the same and in my
head they're not um I believe that
entrepreneurship is that creative aspect
of of of building businesses or just
building ideas that can help people we
have to get our kids thinking creatively
because you know our systems uh
Educational Systems kind of stifle that
creative thinking and you have kids not
knowing what to do with their lives uh
scratching their head and some of them
even kill themselves because they don't
feel like they have purpose when
yeah and I'll tell you that my my
daughter came home I think it was last
semester maybe last school year but she
came home with a um a business plan and
her teacher told her you need to write a
business plan I looked at it for like 10
seconds I said throw this garbage away
this is stupid this is not this is not
how you do a business plan in fact you
don't even need a business plan
depending on you know what stage you're
at and how you're going to build your
business uh we don't have a business
plan for D6 media we have goals we have
objectives but it it's it's evolved so
we leave room for that but we're clear
on our operations and you know so from
that perspective we do and I told her in
school I said get through school get
good grades and both my kids are uh they
either get straight A's depending on the
semester or they they're AB students and
they're always on honoral or principal
list or you know one of those um those
achievements but I told I tell both of
them 80% of what you learn in school get
through school and forget it because
it's useless and as far as College if
you want to go to college and play
sports
awesome if you don't plan to do that and
you don't plan to be a doctor or a
lawyer it's a scam it's a waste of money
go go start a business and you learn
that way so um the education system it
needs to change I'm not a fan of it
because I think it's broken and it's
obsolete uh it's one of the few
institutions in America that hasn't
changed in a hundred plus years and
that's a problem it doesn't keep up to
date and it just gets worse in college
it get more expensive and less
effective wow and and I I agree because
like I I have a learning disability I
have dis well it's not disability for me
it is um like a superpower but I have
dyslexia and I didn't realize I was
smart until I left school and I didn't
you know what I mean like I and I I
didn't realize how intelligent I was
until um until I because I had to teach
myself how to read and teach myself how
to learn and and you know a lot of the
guys that I grew up with you know are
working retail jobs and not really doing
much with their lives you know apart
from you know they got their families
and whatnot and I'm not trying to say my
life is better than theirs or compare
but the reality is that you know the
people that you thought that were doing
so well in school you know um they don't
end up living up to the potential that
you know the school system kind of sets
them out to to yeah to be right yeah so
uh Fraser says do you have a plan to
have any strategic Partnerships to
support and leverage off of partner
companies yeah actually so I mentioned
the partnership deal uh so absolutely um
one of the things you can do when you're
scaling a company if you want to grow
big is you either hire the people and if
you don't have the capital to hire
people you know you don't have the
clients yet what you can do is acquire
companies uh and you can work out deals
so we acquired um a company and it was a
a oneman operation and he's a graphic
designer he's now our business partner
so we just uh we're closing that deal
now where we just did the partnership
agreement tonight and we're going to get
that all signed but he's been working
with us for the last month or so uh so
we saw I saw what he was doing I saw his
vision and realized I can help him get
there with the resources I have and he
can help us fulfill our vision with what
he brings to the table so that was a
strategic partnership uh and you got to
be careful with those again I have me
mentors that I talk to and um W wage
those decisions and get their input um
and sometimes they'll tell me no it's a
bad idea so that's one part partnership
and then we were approached by um a
larger uh agency or they're not really
an agency they they do a they create
products around celebrity Brands um so
they they they're very much um the
product based and e-commerce so they
don't have an agency to fulfill some of
the needs that they have to take on more
clients so they approached us uh through
some mutual friends and uh the president
of the company heard me speak and just
saw my energy invited me to his event
and now we're negotiating that deal and
we'll we'll close that deal before the
end of the year and um that's going to
open up you a huge opportunity and
they're going to acquire a equity in our
company in exchange for us servicing
100% of the celebrity clients that they
bring in uh so mean you just got to put
it out there and be always be on your
aame uh don't I paid to go speak at that
event uh actually I paid to travel out
there and I spoke for at a friends event
and through through his Network we
connected and now it's it's becoming a
huge partnership deal and they're a
company that you know they're a they're
an eight figure company wow that's
that's amazing so we're gonna get into
uh our lightning round um again I'm I'm
working on like getting some graphics
you know some lightning uh bolts but um
you know the first question is do you
prefer talking or
texting um it depends on who if
if it's a high value relationship let
and it's an important topic let's talk
if not let's text okay favorite day of
the
week um Monday everyone hates Mondays
but you know what 3% of the PE 97% of
the people who hate Mondays work for the
3% who don't so stop crying step up or
you're always gonna be at the bottom I
love it uh first celebrity
crush Jessica Alba my wife still teases
me about it I'm waiting for my wife to
become a celebrity and then it'll all be
in alignment
nice nice nice answer uh last song you
downloaded oh you know I don't download
songs but the last song I listened to
today was Rudolph the rednose Reindeer
by DMX the rapper
yes I what exactly that was my reaction
DMX Rudolph the renos reindeer wow okay
uh I'm going to have to download that
afterwards or stream it um Michael
Jackson or
Prince uh Michael Jackson phenomenal
dancer love his music never really got
into Prince can't take pants with the
butt cut
out
no no buttless chaps okay uh so fill in
the blank Taylor Swift
is
classy at what age do you want to
retire when I'm
dead in invisibility or super
strength in visibility I don't have to
hit you hard if you can't see it
coming is it wrong for a vegetarian to
eat animal
crackers I think it's wrong to be a
vegetarian meat is
delicious well folks that concludes
hustles on TV so uh uh AJ uh what did
you think about um today's uh interview
or the experence oh I love it this is I
love your format it it was fun I love
that you had the Facebook comments going
because I can see them I love the
interaction of people asking questions
and I love the lightning round you know
it's yeah I love it we got do it again
yes we we most definitely will uh
because the hustle Zone it's kind of
like a network I mean we're going to be
producing shows um uh exclusively for
certain entrepreneurs so if you want to
produce a show or you want to
collaborate I'm all down for that um
yeah so we have one more thing before we
leave this this this conversation uh we
have uh it's a tradition to the hustle
zone so I'm going to do a call and
response and I need you to yell as loud
as you can um so I'm gonna say uh
welcome to the and then I need you to
say hustle zone or whatever however you
do it but I need it to be loud so one
two three welcome to the hustle
Zone I like that you got I wish I could
I love that I'm going to do that next
time so thank you so much AJ for coming
in
um I just uh my mouse fell but thank you
so much for coming into the show uh
folks this was a great this was a great
interview um wow like you know he he he
gave us everything in a bag of chips so
I I I do appreciate um AJ for coming on
to the show uh folks you know if you
feel that you have a story to tell you
know check us out ww. hustles own.tv and
um you know and and and definitely check
us out go to the living documentary go
to contributors and book time um to get
your story onto the show it won't hurt I
won't hurt um and you know it's a
relaxed conversation and and whatnot and
and don't forget folks um you know I put
a we put a lot of time in and reason
resource um into making this happen um
so definitely check us out on our um let
me just pull us up here if I
can uh check us out on hustle zone.
gofundme.com
hustle Zone hyphen TV donate something
$25 $10 um help us tell more stories
because we want to travel we want to
meet more entrepreneurs and we want to
get more deep in the heart of of of
entrepreneur
uh so make sure you guys check us out
and then we are doing hustle Zone Awards
hustle Zone TV Awards so we're going to
be opening up nominations for you to
vote in your your favorite entrepreneur
and we're going to we're we're hoping to
launch this June 2018 so nominations
will be going up in the next few days so
if you want to get a notification go to
our website and um you know subscribe to
our newsletter so that you could be on
the up and up when those um when those
uh when the nomination form uh launches
so anyways this was great I enjoyed I
enjoyed AJ story so thank you guys folks
for coming in and I will talk to you
later what if there was a docu series
for entrepreneurs that never ended a
living documentary that will continue to
clarify illustrate and unfold
information about the culture that that
surrounds entrepreneurship what if this
docu series was filmed in front of a
live audience all over the world where
sensorship and editing were no longer
applicable when information that is
given to you isn't packaged but
delivered to you raw and fresh honest
and truthful what if you could ask
questions live or help fact check while
someone is speaking well we have already
created this platform and we call it
hustle Zone TV
[Music]
[Applause]
for
e
e e